In this short course,
在这个短期课程中，
you saw a range of applications including processing customer reviews,
您看到了一系列应用程序，包括处理客户评论，
and building an application to answer questions over documents,
并构建一个应用程序来回答有关文档的问题，
and even using an LLM to decide when to make a call to the external tool,
甚至使用LLM来决定何时调用外部工具，
like web search to answer complex questions.
就像网络搜索一样回答复杂的问题。
If a week or two ago,
如果一两周前，
someone had asked you how much work would it be to build all of these applications?
有人问你构建所有这些应用程序需要多少工作？
I think a lot of people would have thought,
我想很多人会想，
"Boy, this sounds like weeks,
“男孩，这听起来像是几个星期，
maybe even longer of work."
也许甚至更长的工作。
But you saw in this short course how with
但是你在这个简短的课程中看到了如何
just a pretty reasonable number of lines of code,
只是相当合理的代码行数，
you can use LLM to build all of these applications pretty efficiently.
您可以使用LLM非常有效地构建所有这些应用程序。
As I hope you take these ideas,
正如我希望你接受这些想法，
maybe you can take some code snippets that you saw in
也许你可以拿一些你在
the Jupyter Notebooks and use them in your own applications.
Jupyter 笔记本，并在您自己的应用程序中使用它们。
These ideas are really just the start.
这些想法实际上只是一个开始。
There's a lot of other applications that you can use language models for.
还有许多其他应用程序可以使用语言模型。
These models are so powerful because they're applicable to
这些模型非常强大，因为它们适用于
such a wide range of tasks whether it be answering questions about CSVs,
如此广泛的任务，无论是回答有关CSV的问题，
querying SQL databases, interacting with APIs.
查询 SQL 数据库，与 API 交互。
There's a lot of different examples of using chains and the combinations of
有很多使用链和组合的不同示例
prompts and output parsers and then more chains to do all these things in LinkedChain.
提示并输出解析器，然后是更多的链来在链接链中执行所有这些操作。
Most of that is due to the LinkedIn community.
其中大部分是由于LinkedIn社区。
So I want to also give a really big thank out to
因此，我也想非常感谢
everyone in the community who's contributed,
社区中做出贡献的每个人，
whether it be improvements in the documentation,
无论是文档的改进，
making it easier for others to get started or new types of chains,
使其他人更容易上手或新型链，
opening up a whole new world of possibilities.
打开一个充满可能性的全新世界。
>> With that, if you have not yet already done so,
>> 有了这个，如果你还没有这样做，
I hope you go to your laptop,
我希望你去你的笔记本电脑，
your desktop and run pip install LinkedChain and then go
你的桌面并运行pip安装链接链，然后去
use this tool to go build some amazing applications.
使用此工具构建一些令人惊叹的应用程序。